MAPS

Basically - just a key value array

DIFFERENCES
- In maps, all key must be of the same type, and all values must be of the same time,
while in structs - field can have different indicies and values for properties, making
structs more sutiable to represent objects with lots of different properties
- In maps, keys are indexed, allowing for iteration, while in structs, keys dont support indexing
- In maps, u dont need to know all of the keys at compile time, while in structs, you need to know all
the different fields at compile time
- Maps are reference types, while structs are value types
